

OSCP | CEH (Master)

#### How to reach me:

#### Cell:

+91 7010951718

#### Email:

akrt@protonmail.com

#### Website

adithyanak.com

#### Blog

blog.adithyanak.com

### **Infosec Skills**

- · Penetration testing
- Offensive Security
- Bug Bounty
- Exploit Development
- Open Source Intelligence
- · Security Research

#### **CVE**

- CVF-2019-6441
- CVE-2019-7562
- CVE-2019-7563
- CVE-2019-7564
- CVE-2019-7565

#### **Education**

# **B.Tech Information Technology**

Aug 2017 - March 2021

Sri Krishna College of Engineering and Technology

## **Personal Profile**

Offensive Security
Researcher with over 4
years of experience.
Skilled in Penetration
Testing, Web
Application Security,
Network Security, and
Red Teaming

## **Programming Skills**

- Python
  - Django Framework
- Bash
- C
- C++
- Java

## **Career Summary**

# OWASP, Coimbatore - Chapter Head

July 2018 - Present

Conduct specialized research in application vulnerabilities and attack vectors, designing and developing open-source tools for application security, contributing to existing OWASP open-source projects, and conducting cybersecurity training and awareness programs.

## Gurugram Cyber cell, Haryana - Intern

May 2019 - June 2019

Researched real-world cybersecurity attacks against people, studied and interpreted cybersecurity laws, and developed security suites to be used by Law Enforcement agencies.

## PrimeFort — Security Analyst (Part-Time)

July 2019 - April 2021

Responsibilities include researching and analyzing new vulnerabilities, web and network penetration testing, source code reviews, threat analysis and wireless network assessments

## Synack Red Team - Red Team Researcher (Part-Time)

April 2021 - Present

Host security assessment, web application penetration tests, Developing comprehensive and accurate reports with proof of concept.

#### **Research & Achievements**

- Top 10 Security Researcher Oppo Bug Bounty Leaderboard 2018.
- Winner at Hac'KP 2020 International Virtual Hackathon by Kerala Police Department
- Winner at SecArmy CTF 2020
- Reverse Engineering and Backdooring Router Firmware IEEE
   International Conference on Advanced Computing and Communication Systems
- LSAF: A Novel Comprehensive Application and Network Security
   Framework for Linux IEEE International Conference on Advanced
   Computing and Communication Systems
- Remote Code Execution in Web Applications International Journal of Engineering and Technology
- Web Application Penetration Testing International Journal of Innovative Technology and Exploring Engineering (IJITEE)
- Runner at TN Police Hackathon conducted by Tamilnadu Police
- Delivered talks at Defcon and OWASP meetups

# **Projects**

## WAVE — Web Application Vulnerability Scanner

A Python-based CLI tool that scans for web application vulnerabilities such as Cross-site scripting, SQL injection, local file inclusion, Host header injection, Clickjacking, and Cross-origin resource sharing.

# OSINTsploit — Framework

A comprehensive OSINT framework built with Python that gathers information about a suspect through a variety of Open Source Intelligence techniques. Additional functionalities include metadata extraction, reverse image search, IP heat map creation, etc.

# Track Their Download — REST API

An API built with Django REST Framework to display torrent download information of a given IPV4 address by scraping from an external source.

## Whatsapp Auto Chat Bot — ChatBot

An Artificially intelligent chatbot built with Python and selenium that can impersonate the user and speak to the user's selected WhatsApp contacts.

#### **Certifications**

- Offensive Security Certified
   Professional (OSCP)
- Certified Ethical Hacker
- <u>Certified Ethical Hacker</u>
   <u>Practical</u>
- <u>Certified Ethical Hacker</u>
   (Master)

# **Hall Of Fame & Recognition**

- Microsoft
- Oppo
- AT&T
- · Apple Security Advisory
- Intel
- Avira

## **Exploits**

- <u>www.exploit-</u> <u>db.com/exploits/46180</u>
- <u>www.exploit-</u> <u>db.com/exploits/46336</u>

# **Author Profiles**

- Exploit-DB
- Cxsecurity
- Packetstormsecurity
- Vulmon
- Github
- Google Scholar

## **Social Handles**

- Instagram
- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- Twitter
- Facebook

#### **Character References**

susila@skcet.ac.in Head of the Department, Information Technology, Sri Krishna College of Engineering and Technology

### Dr. Sivabalan K N

knsbalan@skcet.ac.in Professor, Information Technology, Sri Krishna College of Engineering and Technology